<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Less is more</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Less is more</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Andrey Shuster.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:31:38 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My note-taking journey</title><link>https://example.com/my-note-taking-journey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:31:38 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/my-note-taking-journey/</guid><description>A samurai has no goal, only a path (c).
At some point, the flow of incoming information becomes very large and powerful like the Niagara Falls. Naturally, the thought arises - to WRITE DOWN this information. The second thought is to create a NOTE ORGANIZATION SYSTEM because while writing it down is good, the recorded information needs to be searched and used, preferably with minimal effort between these points.
I&amp;rsquo;ve tried most of the popular note-taking apps, from Notion to Obsidian and OneNote.</description></item><item><title>Todo Lists Are Enough</title><link>https://example.com/todo-lists-are-enough/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 20:34:42 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/todo-lists-are-enough/</guid><description>I always try to organize my workspace using a minimum of tools and simple rules that work for 90% of my tasks. Simple rules are easier to follow, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take much time to get used to them.
For example, managing pet projects. I work on them quite irregularly, with breaks of several days or even a couple of weeks. Context is forgotten, and returning to project tasks takes half an hour, even though I only have an hour of free time for the project.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://example.com/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/pages/about/</guid><description>Hey there, I&amp;rsquo;m Andrey, DevOps specialist and programmer with passion for all things tech, especially cybersecurity and automating things.
My journey has been one of autodidacticism – an odyssey of self-directed learning and practical experience. My foundation was not laid in the traditional confines of a classroom, but rather through a curiosity and desire to unravel the complexities of computers.
I am a big fan of classic science fiction like Isaac Asimov&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Foundation&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;The Futurological Congress&amp;rdquo; by Stanislaw Lem or &amp;ldquo;The Moon is a Harsh Mistress&amp;rdquo; by Robert Heinlein.</description></item></channel></rss>