<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Less is more</title><link>https://andreyshuster.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on Less is more</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Andrey Shuster.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:00:46 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andreyshuster.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Sql Is Important?</title><link>https://andreyshuster.github.io/why-sql-is-important/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:00:46 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://andreyshuster.github.io/why-sql-is-important/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When writing an SQL query, you start with &lt;code&gt;SELECT&lt;/code&gt; and then &lt;code&gt;FROM&lt;/code&gt;
because it resembles human language: first, you say what you want to
get (for example, a list of names), and then you specify where to
get this data from (from the participants table). It&amp;rsquo;s easier to
remember and formulate this way, although all programmers agree that
it would be better the other way around — &lt;code&gt;FROM ... SELECT&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>My note-taking journey</title><link>https://andreyshuster.github.io/my-note-taking-journey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:31:38 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://andreyshuster.github.io/my-note-taking-journey/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A samurai has no goal, only a path (c).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At some point, the flow of incoming information becomes very large and powerful like the Niagara Falls. Naturally, the thought arises - to WRITE DOWN this information. The second thought is to create a NOTE ORGANIZATION SYSTEM because while writing it down is good, the recorded information needs to be searched and used, preferably with minimal effort between these points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve tried most of the popular note-taking apps, from Notion to Obsidian and OneNote. All excellent apps with interesting concepts and rich functionality, but in the end, it became the reason why I rejected them.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Todo Lists Are Enough</title><link>https://andreyshuster.github.io/todo-lists-are-enough/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 20:34:42 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://andreyshuster.github.io/todo-lists-are-enough/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I always try to organize my workspace using a minimum of tools and simple rules that work for 90% of my tasks. Simple rules are easier to follow, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take much time to get used to them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, managing pet projects. I work on them quite irregularly, with breaks of several days or even a couple of weeks. Context is forgotten, and returning to project tasks takes half an hour, even though I only have an hour of free time for the project.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>